KEE HUI LAM

Mobile/ Web Developer

- **98918295**
- % linkedin.com/in/kee-hui-lam
- **9** East, Singapore

- kiwi1@live.com.sg
- % https://github.com/Kiwinoob

ABOUT ME

I interned as Frontend Web Developer at Acumen Bizcorp, I have developed user-facing features and ensured the efficiency of applications using Angular, JavaScript, and TypeScript. This shows dedication to learning and adaptability is reflected in my diverse experiences, from logistics operations to part-time roles in customer service. My education has up to three years of experience align well with the requirement for a motivated and adaptable team player who can facilitate the delivery of quality solutions. I am eager to contribute my skills, and the same time learn, progress, and gain experience on new tech stack opportunities.

EXPERIENCE

10/2020 - 02/2021

Frontend Web Developer -Intern

Singapore

Acumen Bizcorp

- Developing new user-facing features
- · Developing customer experiences using latest technologies
- Ensuring the performance, efficiency, quality, and responsiveness of applications
- Framework used Angular, Programming language used Java Script and TypeScript

09/2017 - 11/2017

Logistics Operations -Intern

Singapore

Singapore

Logistics Worldwide Express

- Scan parcels to database
- · Sorting parcels according to company guideline
- · Delete duplicated parcel data from database
- · Perform other task assigned

12/2016 - 09/2017

Part Time In Universal Studios Singapore Fast-Food Restaurant

Logistics Worldwide Express

- Maintain the cleanness of the fast-food restaurant at any point of time.
- Help Kitchen to Serve food when customer food is delay.
- Provide basic customer service to handle customer inquiries.

EDUCATION

07/2023 - 10/2024

◆ Bachelor of Science in Computing Science

04/2018 - 04/2021 ◆ Diploma in Information Technology

Coventry University

Temasek Polytechnic

01/2017 - 01/2018 ◆ Higher Nitec in Information Technology Institute of Technical Education

• Nitec in Info-communications Technology (Networking & System Administration)

Institute of Technical Education

PROJECTS

Professional Experience

- Collaborate, re-designed and developed Belmacs Pte Ltd's website from scratch, encompassing the entire process from design to deployment on an IIS server. Framework used ReactJS, programing language Typescript and Firebase as database.
- Collaborate to develop a Duty roster planner website for National Service using NextJS framework and Sanity.io as database.

Academic Projects

- Developed a website using NextJS framework, programing language Typescript and Firebase as database for Final Year Project.
- Developed a Timetable and scheduler viewer application using python programing language.
- Developed an IOS application using Xcode and Objective C or Swift as the programming language.
- Developed an Android application using Android Studio and Java as the programming language and database is Google Firebase.
- Developed a Hybrid Mobile Application using Ionic Framework and Database is Google Firebase.
- Developed a website with HTML5, JavaScript, MySql as the Database and express as backend.
- Developed a website for Full-stack Development module with framework Angular, programing language JavaScript and MongoDB as Database.

SKILL

Programing languages

| Java | JavaScript | TypeScript | Objective C | C# | Swift | Python | |
|--------|------------|------------|-------------|----|-------|--------|--|
| | | | | | | | |
| Framev | vork | | | | | | |

| Angular ASP.net Ionic React JS Next J | Angular | ASP.net | Ionic | React JS | Next JS |
|---------------------------------------|---------|---------|-------|----------|---------|
|---------------------------------------|---------|---------|-------|----------|---------|

Soft Skill

| | Teamwork | Communication | n Time Management | Adaptability | Willingness to learn |
|-----------------------------|----------|-----------------|-------------------|--------------|----------------------|
| | | | | | |
| Setting and attaining goals | | attaining goals | Problem solving | | |

LANGUAGES

English Intermediate Chinese Intermediate